http://www.remsystems.co.nz/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Our Security and Privacy Statement
REM SYSTEMS has created this security and privacy statement in order to demonstrate and communicate its commitment to doing business with the highest ethical standards and appropriate internal controls. REM SYSTEMS may periodically require customers to give us contact information (such as name, e-Mail address, and telephone number). This information is used to provide information to those who inquire about our products and services and to get in touch with customers when necessary. Under no circumstances is this information shared with third parties.
Our site is protected with a variety of security measures such as physical access controls, passwords and change control procedures. We also use other mechanisms to ensure that data you provide is not lost, misused, or altered inappropriately. These controls include regular database backups and data confidentiality policies.
If you wish to remove your name and related information from our database, we will promptly take action to comply with your request. We are also able to process address change requests through any of the following communication channels:
Contact REM SYSTEMS Ltd (NEW ZEALAND)
Contact REM SYSTEMS Pty Ltd (AUSTRALIA)
If you have any queries regarding this security and privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with our company, you can contact us using any of the above communication channels.
Freephone
0508 654 258
Main Office
09 570 3322
Customer Service
09 570 3288
© REM SYSTEMS 2014 - 2021
About Us
